Finding Aid for Royal S. Copeland Papers 1892-1938
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Royal S. Copeland Papers 1892-1938
Copeland, Royal S. (Royal Samuel), 1868-1938.
1 oversized folder
45 oversized volumes
37 linear feet
Professor of homoeopathic medicine at University of Michigan, mayor of Ann Arbor, Michigan, dean of the New York Homeopathic Medical College and director of Flower Hospital, New York City Commissioner of Public Health, and Democratic U. S. Senator from New York, 1923-1938. Personal and medical correspondence, speeches, scrapbooks containing food and health articles, photographs, and other papers concerning his medical and political interests. Correspondents include: Calvin Coolidge, Herbert Hoover, Eleanor Roosevelt, Franklin D. Roosevelt, and Alfred E. Smith.
851041 Aa/2, AC, UAm
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection was received from Mrs. Royal S. Copeland (donor no. ( 1240 ) in 1938 and 1940. A second, separate, accession was received from the New York Historical Society (donor no. 4654 ) in 1968.
The collection is open for research.
Royal S. Copeland, physician, public health officer, newspaper columnist, and United States Senator, was born November 7, 1868 in Dexter, Michigan. He received his M.D. degree from the University of Michigan in 1889. After some postgraduate study in Europe, he practiced medicine in Bay City from 1890 to 1895. From 1895 to 1908, he was professor in the Homeopathic Medical College of the University of Michigan. For part of this time from 1901 to 1903, Copeland was elected and served as mayor of Ann Arbor, Michigan.
In 1908, Copeland moved to New York City where he became dean of the Flower Hospital Medical College. Here he developed a reputation as an eye specialist, teacher, and medical writer. In 1918, the mayor of New York selected Copeland to be the city's commissioner of public health. He was an able administrator who used his own newspaper column as well as other publicity to educate the public about matters of health.
In 1922, Copeland was nominated (and later elected) as the compromise Democratic candidate for the United States Senate. He was reelected in 1928 and again in 1934. While in the Senate, Copeland demonstrated a special interest in pure food and drug legislation. He is best known for the Copeland-Lea Food, Drug, and Cosmetic Bill that was passed in 1938 after five years of labor. Although a Democrat, Copeland frequently opposed President Roosevelt and his New Deal legislation. Notably, Copeland was a leading opponent of Roosevelt's court reform plan.
In 1937, Copeland was persuaded to seek the nomination for mayor of New York. He ran in both party primaries and lost in both despite the support of Al Smith.
Copeland died while still serving as a United States senator on June 17, 1938.
The collection has been organized into the following series:
Personal/biographical materials -- Box 1
Correspondence -- Boxes 1-20
Topical -- Boxes 20-24
Campaign Files -- Box 24
United States Senate --Boxes 25-33
Miscellaneous -- Box 34
Clippings -- Boxes 34-35 and outsize volume
Photographs -- Box 36
Sound Recordings -- Box 38
Frances Copeland papers -- Box 36-37
Royal S. Copeland, Jr. papers -- Box 37
The Royal Copeland collection, consisting primarily of correspondence, speeches and writings, scrapbooks, and articles, relates primarily to Copeland's medical career as professor of homeopathic medicine at the University of Michigan, dean of the New York Homeopathic Medical College and Flower Hospital, and New York City Commissioner of Public Health, and as United States Senator.
Subjects:
American newspapers--Sections, columns, etc.; Ann Arbor (Mich.); Copeland, Royal S. (Royal Samuel), 1868-1938.; Copeland family.; Democratic Party (Mich.); Depressions--1929--United States.; Dexter (Mich.); Draft.; Epidemics.; Homeopathy.; Hylan, John F., 1868-1936.; Journalists--United States.; Mayors--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Medicine.; New Deal, 1933-1939.; New York (State)--New York.; New York (State); New York (N.Y.). Board of Health.; New York Medical College.; Physicians--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Physicians--New York (State)--New York.; Public health.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.; Smith, Alfred Emanuel, 1873-1944.; United States. Congress--Elections, 1922.; United States. Congress--Elections, 1928.; United States. Congress--Elections, 1934.; United States--Politics and government--1923-1929.; United States--Politics and government--1933-1945.; United States--Politics and government--1929-1933.; University of Michigan--Faculty.; University of Michigan. Homoeopathic Hospital.; University of Michigan. Medical School.; Wedemeyer, William Walter, 1873-1913.; World War, 1914-1918.
Subjects - Visual Material:
Buildings--Michigan--Dexter.; Cadillac (Mich.); Cadillac (Mich.)--Dwellings.; Churches--Michigan--Dexter.; Copeland family.; Copeland, Royal S. (Royal Samuel), 1868-1938.; Dexter (Mich.)--Buildings.; Dexter (Mich.)--Churches.; Dexter (Mich.)--Dwellings.; Dwellings--Michigan--Cadillac.; Dwellings--Michigan--Dexter.; Interiors--Domestic--1900.; Kinyon, Claudius Bligh, b. 1851.; Lindbergh, Charles A. (Charles Augustus), 1902-1974.; Travel.
Contributors:
Coolidge, Calvin, 1872-1933.; Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964.; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962.
Genre/Form:
Photographs.; Scrapbooks.; Tintypes.
- Personal/biographical materials
  Personal/biographical materials is a small series of collected biographical information about Copeland and the Copeland family. Within this series has been placed the scattering of papers of Copeland forebears. There are two letters of Will Holmes to Francis Holmes Copeland written while serving in the Civil War. The letters are dated 1862 and 1864.
  - Biographical materials (Box 1)
  - Copeland family genealogy, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Civil War correspondence of Will Holmes to Francis (Holmes) Copeland 1862, 1864 (Box 1)
  - Family correspondence undated, 2 folders (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1892-1938, 19 linear feet
  The Copeland Correspondence series is voluminous, dating from 1892 to 1938. The bulk of this correspondence, however, is 1907 to 1934. Much of the correspondence concerns his career in medicine and medical administration. Included is correspondence with patients, with physicians, and with other medical administrators. There is also social and personal correspondence. A lesser amount of these files pertains to political or legislative activities.
  - 1886-1887 (Box 1)
    (letters received as a student)
  - 1888 (Box 1)
  - 1892-1900 (Box 1)
  - 1901-1903 (Box 1)
  - 1904 (Box 1)
  - 1905, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 1906, 9 folders (Box 1)
  - January-October 1907, 10 folders (Box 1)
  - November-December 1907, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - 1908, 20 folders (Box 2)
  - 1909 undated, January-March 1909, 7 folders (Box 2)
  - April-December 1909, 19 folders (Box 3)
  - 1910 undated, January-April 1910, 12 folders (Box 3)
  - May-December 1910, 20 folders (Box 4)
  - 1911 undated, January 1911, 4 folders (Box 4)
  - February-December 1911, 26 folders (Box 5)
  - 1912 undated (Box 5)
  - 1912, 23 folders (Box 6)
  - 1913 undated, January-February 1913, 5 folders (Box 6)
  - March-December 1913, 11 folders (Box 7)
  - 1914 undated, January-October 1914, 15 folders (Box 7)
  - November-December 1914, 4 folders (Box 8)
  - 1915, 22 folders (Box 8)
  - 1916 undated, January 1916, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - January-December 1916, 22 folders (Box 9)
  - 1917 undated, January-May 1917, 8 folders (Box 9)
  - June-December 1917, 9 folders (Box 10)
  - 1918 undated, January-September 1918, 20 folders (Box 10)
  - October-December 1918, 4 folders (Box 11)
  - 1919, 21 folders (Box 11)
  - 1920, 16 folders (Box 12)
  - 1921 undated, January-March 1921, 8 folders (Box 12)
  - April-December 1921, 16 folders (Box 13)
  - 1922 undated, January-April 1922, 11 folders (Box 13)
  - May-October 1922, 20 folders (Box 14)
  - October-December 1922, 13 folders (Box 15)
  - 1923, 7 folders (Box 15)
  - 1924 (Box 15)
  - 1925, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - 1926, 4 folders (Box 16)
  - 1927, 4 folders (Box 16)
  - 1928 undated, January-October 1928, 12 folders (Box 16)
  - October-December 1928, 7 folders (Box 17)
  - 1929, 4 folders (Box 17)
  - 1930, 14 folders (Box 17)
  - 1931, 10 folders (Box 18)
  - 1932, 9 folders (Box 18)
  - 1933, 4 folders (Box 18)
  - 1934 undated, January-October 1934, 28 folders (Box 19)
  - October-December 1934, 11 folders (Box 20)
  - 1935 (Box 20)
  - 1936, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - 1937 (Box 20)
  - 1938 (Box 20)
  - Undated, 2 folders (Box 20)
- Topical (correspondence, speeches, writings) undated, 1908-1938, 4 linear feet
  The Topical series was drawn together from various subject-related folders. The contents of the folders consists of correspondence, speeches, and various writings. Topics with substantial information relate to homeopathy, Copeland's career with the New York City Department of Health and the New York Homeopathic Medical College and Flower Hospital, and to matters of health in general.
  - Ann Arbor business activities 1925-1928 (Box 20)
  - Ann Arbor city government (Box 20)
  - Ann Arbor mayoralty and business interests (Box 20)
  - Ann Arbor public schools (Box 20)
  - Ball, Joseph October 1909-May 1910 (Box 20)
    (correspondence re. medical situation at the University of Michigan medical school and in New York City)
  - "Camp Copeland" 1925 (Box 20)
  - "Copeland Restaurants" 1925-1930, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - "Copeland Services" 1925 (Box 20)
  - "Dexter Poultry Company" of New York City 1927-1929 (Box 20)
  - Education for Character 1936-1938 (Box 20)
    (correspondence concerning proposed book)
  - Florida properties 1925-1928, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Flower Hospital Unit activities during World War I, May-November 1917, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Fordham National Bank (establishment, etc.) January-August 1925, 3 folders (Box 21)
  - "Guard Your Health" 1924-1925 (Box 21)
    (correspondence concerning health recording)
  - "Guard Your Health" Corporation 1924-1930 (Box 21)
  - Health, mainly RSC speeches and articles, 5 folders (Box 21)
  - Homeopathy, mainly RSC speeches and articles, 6 folders (Box 21)
  - Homeopathy: Reports, constitutions, programs, proposals, and other organizational materials (Box 21)
  - Homeopathy: Lists (Box 21)
  - Homeopathy: Definitions (Box 21)
  - Homeopathy: Printed materials (Box 21)
  - Inter-Collegiate Committee of the American Institute of Homeopathy Record book 1901-1910 (Box 21)
  - Medical advice column questions 1920-1921, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - New York City Department of Health
    - Correspondence with John F. Hylan, mayor of New York City April-May 1918, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Congratulations upon appointment as commissioner May-August 1918, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Writings and speeches, 4 folders (Box 22)
    - Departmental activities, 3 folders (Box 22)
    - Topical files
      - Drug addiction (Box 22)
      - Epidemics (Box 22)
      - Industrial health and safety, 3 folders (Box 22)
      - New York City coal shortage crisis 1917-1919 (Box 22)
      - New York City coal shortage crisis January-February 1923 (Box 22)
    - Printed material (Box 22)
  - New York Homeopathic Medical College and Flower Hospital
    - Accounts and budgets, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Agreements between college and hospital 1911, 1915 (Box 23)
    - Alumni Association 1912-1918 (Box 23)
    - Board of Ambulance Service 1910-1913 (Box 23)
    - Board of Trustees
      - Annual reports from the dean 1910-1914 (Box 23)
      - Reports and minutes 1911-1916 (Box 23)
    - Flower Hospital operations book 1914-1917 (Box 23)
    - Hospital activities undated, 1908-1918, 4 folders (Box 23)
    - Inspection reports 1909-1917, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Investigations 1908-1910 (Box 23)
    - Legislation on health 1909-1915 (Box 23)
    - Lists of enrolled and potential students (Box 23)
    - Medical organizations 1910-1918 (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - New York State Committee of National Defense and related World War I activities 1917-1918 (Box 23)
    - Printed materials (Box 23)
    - Resolutions and bylaws 1915-1917 (Box 23)
    - Staff undated (Box 23)
    - Teaching and student activities 1908-1917 (Box 23)
    - Testimonial dinner for RSC 1908 (Box 23)
    - University of California Homeopathic Medical School merger 1915 (Box 23)
    - Writings and speeches (Box 23)
  - Nyack Daily News (correspondence concerning) 1926-1927 (Box 24)
  - Selective Service deferments for medical students August-November 1917 (Box 24)
  - Tuberculosis cure 1925-1928, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - University of Michigan, Faculty Fund September-November 1930 (Box 24)
  - University of Michigan Medical School reorganization 1920-1922 (Box 24)
  - University of Michigan Medical School (general) (Box 24)
- Campaign files 1922-1934, 0.3 linear feet
  Campaign Files is a small series arranged by date of election campaign and consisting mainly of speeches.
  - 1922
    - Political speeches, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Campaign lists, etc. (Box 24)
  - 1928
    - Contributions (Box 24)
    - Correspondence with Senator Jesse H. Metcalf, Chairman of the Republican Senatorial Committee (Box 24)
    - Correspondence with Gertrude Duncan, Secretary of Women's Democratic League (Box 24)
    - Endorsements (Box 24)
    - Lists (Box 24)
    - Political speeches, 3 folders (Box 24)
    - Pamphlets concerning "Catholic Issue" (Box 24)
  - 1930
    - Political speeches (Box 24)
  - 1932
    - Political speeches, etc. (Box 24)
  - 1934
    - Political speeches, etc. (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous political materials (Box 24)
  - Campaign posters, advertisements, etc. (Box 24)
- U.S. Senate 1923-1938 (mainly speeches), 9 linear feet
  Copeland's United States Senate papers are comparatively sparse for the period of time that he served in office. These files, consisting mainly of speeches, are arranged both by date and by subject. In addition, this series includes a sampling of the views of constituents on Roosevelt's proposed Supreme Court reorganization plan in 1937.
  - By Subject
    - Agriculture (Box 25)
    - Commencements and commemorations (Box 25)
    - Crime and education (Box 25)
    - District of Columbia (Box 25)
    - Economy, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Food and Drug legislation (Box 25)
    - Foreign affairs and immigration (Box 25)
    - General, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Government (Box 25)
    - Health (Box 25)
    - Labor and unemployment (Box 25)
    - Merchant marine (Box 25)
    - Michigan (Box 25)
    - New Deal (Box 25)
    - Political parties (Box 25)
    - Prohibition (Box 25)
    - St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 25)
    - Supreme court (Box 25)
    - Tammany hall (Box 25)
    - Transportation (Box 25)
    - Veterans (Box 25)
    - Water pollution (New York City) (Box 25)
    - Western trip 1927 (Box 25)
    - Women (Box 25)
  - By date
    - 1923-1924 (Box 26)
    - 1925 (Box 26)
    - 1946 (Box 26)
    - 1927 (Box 26)
    - January-August 1928 (Box 26)
    - September-December 1928 (Box 26)
    - 1929 (Box 26)
    - 1930 (Box 26)
    - January-April 1931 (Box 26)
    - May-December 1931 (Box 26)
    - 1932 (Box 26)
    - 1933 (Box 26)
    - 1934 (Box 26)
    - 1935 (Box 26)
    - 1926 (Box 26)
    - January-April 1937 (Box 26)
    - May-December 1937 (Box 26)
    - 1938 (Box 26)
    - Various manuscripts, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Assorted pamphlets
    - On foreign and domestic matters (Box 26)
  - Constituent mail on subject of Supreme Court Reorganization Plan 1937
    - Unprocessed (Box 27)
    - Unprocessed (Box 28)
    - Unprocessed (Box 29)
    - Unprocessed (Box 30)
    - Unprocessed (Box 31)
    - Unprocessed (Box 32)
    - Unprocessed (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous circa 1890-1939
  Miscellaneous is an artificially created series of various personal and professional items, such as appointment books, patients books from the 1890s, and a travel diary from 1929.
  - Appointment books/calendars 1928-1939, 8 v.; some gaps (Box 34)
  - Education for Character (manuscript of proposed book) (Box 34)
  - Eye examination book (industrial accidents) 1914-1918 (Box 34)
  - Guest book 1925-1937 (Box 34)
  - Health articles (notebook containing drafts of) circa 1922 (Box 34)
  - Patients book circa 1890 (Box 34)
  - Patients book 1896 (Box 34)
  - Student notebook, University of Michigan 1888 (Box 34)
  - Travel diary 1929 (Box 34)
- Newspaper clippings/scrapbooks 1901-1938, 45 oversize volumes; 1 linear foot
  The Newspaper clippings/scrapbooks series is a rich source of information about Copeland and his views on health and diet. This extensive series of scrapbooks includes subseries of volumes arranged by date as well as volumes of Copeland newspaper articles on health and food.
  - Clippings
    - Newspaper obituaries 1938 (Box 34)
    - Newspaper clippings concerning Ann Arbor Mayoralty 1901-1903 (Box 34)
    - Newspaper clippings, 5 folders (Box 34)
  - Scrapbooks
    - 1908-1911 (Box 35)
    - 1911 (Box 35)
    - 1928 concerning the election campaign (Box 35)
    - 1938 of newspaper obituaries (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous scrapbooks (Box 35)
  - Oversized scrapbooks
    (separately shelved with AC volumes)
    - By date
      - January-December 1919 (Volume 1)
      - December 1919-September 1921 (Volume 2)
      - [Oversize volume no. 3] (Volume 3)
      - March-December 1921 (Volume 4)
      - December 1921-September 1922 (Volume 5)
      - September-November 1922 (Volume 6)
      - January 1924-May 1925 (Volume 7)
      - May 1925-May 1928 (Volume 8)
      - September-December 1928 (Volume 9)
      - January 1929-March 1930 (Volume 10)
      - March 1930-October 1931 (Volume 11)
      - October 1931-March 1933 (Volume 12)
      - March-November 1933 (Volume 13)
      - November 1933-April 1934 (Volume 14)
      - May 1933-June 1935 (Volume 15)
      - June 1935-January 1937 (Volume 16)
      - February 1937-July 1937 (Volume 17)
      - July 1937 (Volume 18)
      - July-August 1937 (Volume 19)
      - August-September 1937 (Volume 20)
      - Memorial Scrapbook 1938 (Volume 21)
      - September-October 1937, September 1937-May 1938 (Volume 21-a)
      - September-October 1934, September 1937-December 1938 (Volume 44)
    - Health articles
      - November 1920-September 1921 (Volume 22)
      - October 1921-September 1922 (Volume 23)
      - November 1922-August 1923 (Volume 24)
      - September 1923-December 1924 (Volume 25)
      - December 1924-December 1925 (Volume 26)
      - January 1926-November 1927 (Volume 27)
      - November 1927-October 1929 (Volume 28)
      - October 1929-October 1931 (Volume 29)
      - October 1931-September 1933 (Volume 30)
      - October 1933-April 1936 (Volume 31)
      - April 1936-June 1938 (Volume 32)
    - Food articles
      - January 1922-April 1926 (Volume 33)
      - May 1926-August 1928 (Volume 34)
      - August 1928-September 1931 (Volume 35)
      - October 1931-July 1934 (Volume 36)
      - July 1934-May 1937 (Volume 37)
      - May 1937-April 1938 (Volume 38)
    - Political Correspondence
      - September 1922-March 1923 (Volume 39)
      - September 1922-March 1923 (Volume 40)
        (continued)
      - September 1922-March 1923 (Volume 41)
      - September 1922-March 1923 (Volume 42)
      - September 1922-March 1923 (Volume 43)
- Photographs, 1 linear foot
  (also photos in oversized folder UAm and UAx)
  The Photographs in the Copeland collection include portraits and informal photos of Copeland, His wife, and other members of the Copeland family. There are also photos of various Copeland residences, including one in Dexter, Michigan. Also of interest are photos of various political and medical meetings, including a reception for Charles Lindbergh in 1927.
  - Mayor of Ann Arbor, Director of the New York Flower Hospital, and Commissioner of the New York Board of Health (Box 36)
  - U.S. Senator 1922-1938 (Box 36)
  - Miscellaneous, 5 x 7 prints and smaller (Box 36)
  - In groups (Box 36)
  - Snapshots (Box 36)
  - Portraits of Frances S. Copeland (Box 36)
  - Snapshots of Frances S. Copeland (Box 36)
  - Portraits of Royal and Frances Copeland (Box 36)
  - Snapshots of Royal and Frances Copeland (Box 36)
  - Portraits of Royal S. Copeland, Jr. (Box 36)
  - Snapshots of Royal S. Copeland, Jr. (Box 36)
  - Alice Frances Copeland (Box 36)
  - Roscoe, Frances and Cornelia Copeland (Box 36)
  - Mahwah, New Jersey home (Box 36)
  - Suffern, New York home (Box 36)
  - Venice, Florida home (Box 36)
  - Dexter, Michigan. (Box 36)
  - Miscellaneous photographs (Box 36)
  - Copeland family (Box 36)
  - Spalding family (Alice, Adaline, Lyman and others) (Box 36)
  - Reception of Charles A. Lindbergh in New York City 1927 (Box 36)
  - Al Smith (Box 36)
  - Bonus demonstration (Box 36)
  - European and Middle-East trips (Box 36)
  - Photographic album of Frances S. Copeland (Box 36)
    (include views of Cadillac, Mich.; and home interiors)
- Sound Recordings, 1925
  The Sound Recordings include vinyl discs of health talks and exercises as well as a cassette copy of the discs.
  - Discs of health lectures and exercises circa 1925 (Box 38)
    (cassette copy available)
  - Discs of "Guard Your Health" series circa 1925, 5 phonograph records (Box 38)
- Frances S. Copeland papers 1911-1943, 0.5 linear feet
  The Frances Copeland series consists mainly of her correspondence on personal and family matters.
  - Typescripts of articles, including "The Good Guest"; "Ladies of the Senate"; and personal memories (Box 36)
  - Correspondence
    - undated, 4 folders (Box 36)
    - undated, 5 folders (Box 37)
    - 1911, 1915-1925 (Box 37)
    - 1926 (Box 37)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 37)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 37)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 37)
    - 1935 (Box 37)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 37)
    - 1938, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - 1939, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - 1940, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - 1941, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - 1943-1943 (Box 37)
  - Notebook concerning stocks and bonds (Box 37)
- Royal S. Copeland, Jr. papers 1914-1941, 0.5 linear feet
  The Royal S. Copeland, Jr. papers includes personal and family correspondence, also files relating to his campaign for the office of supervisor of Ramapor, New York in 1939, and papers concerning organized reserves and military preparation in the period of 1930 to 1941.
  - Correspondence
    - undated (Box 37)
    - 1914-1934 (Box 37)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 37)
    - 1937-1939 (Box 37)
    - 1940 (Box 37)
    - 1941-1943 (Box 37)
  - Campaign for the office of supervisor of Ramapor, New York 1939 (Box 37)
  - Papers concerning organized reserves, pre-World War II military preparation 1930-1941 (Box 37)
Selective name and subject index
Coolidge, Calvin, 1872-1933.
June 3, 1926, 1927, Jan. 8 and 30, 1929 and Feb. 8, 1929
Epidemics
(Material concerning the influenza epidemic in New York City)
1918-1922
Hoover, Herbert Clark, 1874-1964.
Jan. 14, 1929, Feb. 8, 1929 and 1930
Military service, compulsory
(Material concerning Copeland's efforts to obtain selective service deferments for medical students at the University of Michigan)
1917
Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962.
1922 undated, May 8, 1924, Sept. 29, 1926 and Nov. 1, 1928
Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1882-1945.
Oct. 27, 1922, Jan. 7, 1924, Nov. 26, 1924, Jan. 25, 1926, Dec. 26, 1928, 1929, 1930, Feb. 23 and 28, 1931, 1932, Mar. 13, 1933, July 19, 1933 and Feb. 8, 1937
Smith, Alfred Emanuel, 1873-1944.
Dec. 3, 1923
Wedemeyer, William Walter, 1873-1918.
(Material concerning Wedemeyer's term as Michigan Congressman)
1911-1912